Guide to the Stanford Tape Collection ARS.0112
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 2. Spoken (Lectures, Speeches, Readings, Panel Discussions, Meetings, Hearings, etc.)
  - Committee Meetings/Hearings (Advising/Counseling, Steering, Admissions/Financial Aid)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. June 18th, 1968 (0-1157); Side 2. June 9th, 1968 (0-420), June 11th (420-930), June 13th, 1968 (930-2312), 1968-06; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee. Side 1. June 25th (0-320), June 27th (320-1380) Side 2. June 20th (0-1000), June 25th (1000-2314), 1968-06; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Admissions and Financial Aid Side 2. Steering Committee (0-1065), 1968-07-03; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Admissions 7/9/1968 Side 2. Advising and Counseling 11/17 (0-988) Int. Ed. Hearing with Dwight Clark (988-end), 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Steering Committee July 9, 1968 (0-987), July 10, 1968 (1000-end) Side 2. Committee on Government Univ. 6/19/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee. Interviews 2/3 - Rosch, Carlson, Osborn, Shanalan, Lieberman, M'Connegdy, Grisson, Stillings, Welsch, Reedy, Lewis, Cow, Levine, Shapiro, Rosenbly, Manley, 1968-07-10; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. July 16 (0-353), July 17 (355-1800) Side 2. July 11, 1968 (0-1250), July 16 (1250-2365), 1968-07; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. July 23 (0-1196), July 24 (1200-end) Side 2. July 30 (370 - 1140), 1968-07; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Govt. Committee. Steering Committee 7/31/68 (342-1655). Side 2. Steering Committee (655-850), 8/1/68 (851-1985), 8/6/68 (1990-end), 1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. 8/8/68 (begin - 1255) Side 2. 8/6/68 (0-725), 8/7/68 (End 1232), 1968-08; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. August 20 (0-160) Side 2. July 18 (0-1050), August 20 (1050-2350), 1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Black on CT Sept. 20 (0-450) Sept. 24 (450-1063). Steering Committee Sept. 24 (1063-2295). Side 2. Steering Committee Sept. 24 (0-342), Sept. 26 ( 343 - 1894), 1968-09; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. Oct. 12 (0-545), Oct. 18 (545-end) Side 2. Oct. 18 ( 0-745), 1968-10; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Advising and Counseling Oct. 23 (0-942), Nov. 1 (960-2100). Side 2. Steering Committee May 1 (0-937), Advising and Counseling Nov. 6 (960-1575), 1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. Nov 8 (0-857) Side 2. Oct. 25 (0-805), Nov. 1 (805-1800), 1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee Side 1. 12/11/68 Side 2. 12/13/1968, 1968-12; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - 1. Admissions and Financial Aid Committee 12/11/1967; 1/9/1968; 2/13/1968 2. Steering Committee 2/14, 3/23, 1967-1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid Side 1. 7/8/1968 Side 2. 6/7/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Council of Presidents, 1971-05-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Demonstrations, 1970
    No other information enclosed about the contents. Possibly related to anti-ROTC protests occuring around this time.
    - Demonstrations. Reel 1 - KZSU. B4/1-4/2/70, 1970-04-01; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Demonstrations. Reel 2a - KZSU. B4/1-4/2/70, 1970-04-01; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Demonstrations. Reel 2b - KZSU. B4/1-4/2/70, 1970-04-01; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Demonstration Meeting. Reel 1 of 3, 1970-04-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Demonstration Meeting. Reel 2 of 3, 1970-04-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Demonstration Meeting. Reel 3 of 3. Pauling and Wade, 1970-04-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Charles Dickens, A Christmas Carol. KZSU production, introduced by Virgil Whitaker; cast--various SU staff and faculty, including President Sterling as Jacob Marley. November-December 1964, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Richard Dillon, Librarian, Sutro Library. Perpetual Motion and Emotion. Bender Room, Stanford University Library, 1964-02-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Sandy Dornbusch, Reel 1, 1971-05-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - EE-380 Allison, W.O.#008453--ERL 450 [unidentified], 1 videocassette VHS (Audio 6)
  - Emergency Committee Against Escalation Meeting (Cranston). Reel 1-2, 1971-02-22; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 5)
  - Ful [illegible] nd (RW) [unidentified], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Stuart Frazer Interview. Reel 1, 1971-01-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Dr. David Noel Freedman, The Ancient Library at Ebla, Syria. Annenberg Auditorium, 4:30pm, 1977-04-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Allen Ginsberg poetry reading. Kresge Auditorium., 1984-10-08; 2.0 7" open reel tape(s) (Box 13)
  - Edward Ginzton Interviews. Henry Lowood, Primary Interviewer. Bruce Hevly, Other Interviewer. Copied 1989 from Stanford Oral History Project cassettes in University Archives SV4a-i. 11/11/1987, 12/9/1987, 2/10/1988, 3/23/1988, 1987-1988; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
  - Girard-Siegel panel, 1970-11-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Haas lecture series
    - Leon Lipson. Distinctiveness in Argument. April 22, 1969; The Soviet Point of View. April 23, 1969. William Haas Memorial Lectures, 1969-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Leon Lipson, Some Tasks and Themes in Soviet Polemic. William Haas Memorial Lecture, 1969-04-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Rabbi Abraham Heschel, In Search of Meaning. Who is Man? series [only one of three in series recorded], 1963-01-31; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - David Hilbert talk on mathematics (in German). Recorded from instantaneous discs owned by Prof. Szego, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Herbert Hoover. Speech at Auditorium, Feb.12, 1940 (H.H. 1); Stanford Library dedication, June 20, 1941 (H.H. 2); Wealth of the West #4 Educational Resources (H.H. 9) [see ARS Audio misc. for others in series], 1940-1941; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Humanitas, A Program for Human Unification. Hank Levine, Martha McDougle, Michael Lindemann. Produced by The Bridge, Stanford University, 1974-08-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - IJB (Interim Judicial Body) Sit-in, Old Union, 1968-06
    - IJB Sit in. Tape 1. ASSU General Meeting In Old Student Union; Memorial Auditorium Meeting. 7:30pm, 1968-05-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 2. Meeting, Memorial Auditorium. 8:30pm, 1968-05-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 3. Meeting, Memorial Auditorium and Student Reaction at Union. 10:40pm. KZSU, 1968-05-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 4. Student Discussion, Tactics, Old Union. 11:30pm, 1968-05-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 5. Student Discussion, Old Union. Packard. 10:00pm, 1968-05-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 6. Student Discussion, Old Union. Packard, Ruotolo, students. 11pm, 1968-05-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 7. Taubman Secret Meeting [crossed out] 10:30am, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 9. Union Discussion, 1:30 pm, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 11. Academic Council Results 7:40pm KZSU, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 12. Union Discussion, Decision to Leave Union if Demands Accepted (as reported by Otto) 4:15pm, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 12 [sic]. Discussion Over Idea of Leaving, Answer in Affirmative, First of [ASSU president Cesare] Massarenti's Closing Statements. 8:40pm, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - IJB Sit-in. Tape 13. Last of Massarenti's Closing Statement. KZSU Wrap Up (Otto). 9:40pm, 1968-05-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - David Starr Jordan, Spirit of Stanford 8/1916. Opening of William R. Moran presentation, The Collection and Preservation of Sound (program celebrating 20th Anniversary of ARS) Annenberg Auditorium [program enclosed], 1978-12-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Donald Kennedy inauguration. Frost Amphitheater., 1980-10-12; 1.0 7" open reel tape(s) (Box 7)
  - Arthur Koestler, The Emotional Factors in the Creative Process. Memorial Auditorium. Tape W-32 [KZSU recording form enclosed], 1965-02-23; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - KPFA tape. Panel discussion re: strike [from recent summary enclosed], 1964-04-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Laos Teach-In, Dinkelspiel Auditorium. Reel 1-3, 1971-02-17; 3 7" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
  - Janet Lewis reading at Stanford, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
  - Lyman [presumed all Richard W. Lyman], 1970-1971
    - President Lyman, Freshman Convocation. 7:00pm [KZSU announcer script enclosed], 1970-09-25; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Lyman Press Conference, 1970-10-01; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Lyman press conference, 1970-10-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman Close-up Press Conference, 1970-10-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman, 1970-11-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman press conference, 1970-11-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman, Close-Up, 1970-11-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman's Press Conference, Budget, 1970-11-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman Conference, 1970-12-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman Panel, 1971-01-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman interview, 1971-01-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman - News Conference, 1971-02-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman - Sienna Interviews (With Disclaimer), 1971-02-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - Lyman interview, 1971-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman conference and faculty debate, 1971-05-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Lyman, Faculty Debates, 1971-05-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Léonide Massine lecture and interview. Lucille Nixon School, Palo Alto. Leslie Getz, moderator; Janice Ross, Patricia Egan, Michael Clemens, Gay Weaver, panelists, 1977-05-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - McClatchey lecture series
    - John Chancellor. Ho, Che, Mao, Dick, and Spiro. McClatchey lecture series, 1970-11-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Pete McClosky. Community Forum '70. Reel 1, 1970-10-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - B. McKay, Crisis in Quebec, 1970-10-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Memorial Auditorium, C.A.W.I. [or C.A.W.?] Reel 1, 19uu-02-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Memorial Auditorium Reel 3 [date illegible, poss. 1971], 19uu-02-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Frank O'Connor reading. Dinkelspiel Auditorium. Transferred 1987, 1961-04-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - One Night in Palo Alto, 1970-10-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - PACE (Plan of Action for A Challenging Era) fundraising campaign
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. President Sterling Introduction 2.Professor Hilgard's Welcome 3. Professor Thurman. Reel 1, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Professor Panofsky 2. Professor Guerard. Reel 2, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Professor Guerard 2. Professor Hilgard 3. Question and Answer Period. Reel 3, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Mr. W. Noel Eldred 2.Mr. Morris M. Doyle. Reel 6, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Mr. Charles Ducommun 2. Mr. David Packard. Reel 7, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Mr. Packard Continued 2. Rickeys Introduction 3. Thomas Pike. Reel 8, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Student Panel Continued 2. Mr. Christenson. Reel 12, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - PACE Leadership Conference - 1. Mr Christenson 2. Mr.Shimp 3. Mr. Packard 4. Mr. Pike 5. Mr. Cuthbertson 6. Dean Pettit. Reel 13, 1961-10-27; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Sterling, PACE students. Reels 1-2, 1961-11-06; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
  - Dr. Wolfgang Panofsky, Arms Race, 1971-02-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Dr. Wolfgang Panofsky. High Energy Physics and SLAC: Past and Future. Dinkelspiel Auditorium 7:45pm, 1965-04-27; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Perspectives CC-02 [correspondence from Mary Daniel to Ed Linotti enclosed], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Dr. Norman Philbrick, Garrick's London. Albert M. Bender Room, Stanford University Library, 1969-10-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - PMC [unidentified], 1971-06-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Prince Lightfoot presentation, 1972-11-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Tom Reeves Pete Knudsen Interview, 1971-01-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Tom Reeves Draft Talk, 1971-01-28; 1 7" open reel tape folders (Audio 5)
  - Dr. Richmond [Japanese Sony PR-150 tape], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockfeller Speech at Stanford [signed KZSU broadcast release form enclosed], 1964-01-04; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - [Robert M.?] Rosensweig, 1971-03-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Vermont Royster, The American Press and The Revolutionary Tradition. Distinguished lecture series on the Bicentennial. Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 8:00pm, 1974-03-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Sea Gull, drama. Larry Liebert for Close-Up. Reel 1, 1970-11-19; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Senior Class in Memorial Auditorium, 1972-06-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - William Shockley Debate. Taped by Paul Loeb [article reprints enclosed], 1971-06-02; 1 7" open reel tape folder (Audio 5)
  - Mark Shorer. Albert M. Bender Room, Stanford University Library, 1968-10-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Leon Sloss Junior Memorial Visiting Lectureship series
    General note
    See also Gunther Schuller lecture under Music series
    - Stanley Cavell, Afterthoughts on Film. Sloss lecture, 1973-11-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Michel Butor, Travel and Creative Writing. Bishop Auditorium. Leon Sloss Junior Memorial Visiting Lectureship, 1973-11-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Lord Ashby. Sloss lectures. 1. 10/9/1977 2. 10/10/1977 3. 10/11/1977. Reels 1-2, 1977-10; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
  - Kenneth Stephen Smith, Barbara Smuts, Dr. David Hamburg. First US press conference concerning kidnapping of Stanford students in Tanzania by rebels in Zaire. Tresidder Memorial Union, Room 270, 1975-08-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Lewis W. Spitz, The Power of the Word. Special Collections exhibit, Albert M. Bender Room, Stanford University Library, 3:30pm, 1968-04-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Stanford Judicial Council - Michael Holman Trial, 1971-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Stanford Judicial Council Hearing - Moot Court Room, Lodge Defenders, 1971-01-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Chancellor Sterling Reception at Faculty Club, 1974-04-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Corporate luncheon. Dr. Sterling, Mr. TSP, Mr. Packard; David Packard, presiding. Jim Black. Cubberly Auditorium, Saturday AM, 1963-05-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Lois Meek Stoltz (Professor of Psychology, Emeritus), Women in Stanford History. ASSU Reception Honoring Stanford Women; Richard Lyman, Campus Conference (1975?), 1975-04-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Christening of the S.S. Kings Canyon, honoring Stanford Professor Lois M. Stolz (from instantaneous discs owned by granddaughter Lois M. Stolz, transferred 7/85), 1945-03-24; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Strike Meeting. Ira Sandperl, George Solomon, Dr. Tom Bittker. Philosophy Department Discussion on Proposals to Academic Senate, 1970-05-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - F.E. Terman, President, Vice-Provost, Stanford. KPEN, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Dr. Terman I and II (Recorded by James Stultz on Ampex 400a, 2 7" open reel tapes folders (Audio 8)
  - Admiral True, UN vets. Bill Pease, Close-Up, 1970-10-28; 1 7" open reel tape folders (Audio 5)
  - Tuesday Evening lecture series
    - Dr. Walter Goldschmidt, On Being An African Today. Introduction by Prof. Spindler. Dinkelspiel 7:45pm [announcer script enclosed] Tuesday Evening lecture series, 1965-05-11; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Prof. Robert McAfee Brown, What's New in Religion? Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1972-03-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. John Kaplan, Marijuana--The New Prohibition. Tressider Memorial Union. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1972-11-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Jane Goodall, The Behavior of Chimpanzees in their Natural Habitat. Memorial Auditorium. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1972-12-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Dr. Linus Pauling, Prevention of Disease. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1973-01-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Katchadourian. Non-Sexual Uses of Sex. Memorial Auditorium. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1973-04-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Philip Zimbardo. Generation vs. Here and Gone. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1973-10-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Conceptual Blockbusting. Tressider Lounge, 8pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1973-11-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - John Lewis. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1973-12-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Dt. Henry S. Kaplan, The Paradox of Radiation and Cancer: Both Cause and Cure. Memorial Auditorium, 8:00pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1974-01-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - [Philip] Rhinelander. Tuesday Evening Lecture series, 1974-03-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Diane Middlebrook, The Unborn Androgyne. Memorial Auditorium, 8:00pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1974-04-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Alfredo Castenada, Cultural Democracy in Education. Tuesday Evening Lecture series, 1974-05-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Barbara Babcock, Professional Responsibilities and Ordinary Morals: A Comparative Analysis for the Legal Profession. Tuesday evening Lecture Series, 1974-10-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Robert Ward, Our relations with Japan: a long range view. Tressider Memorial Union Lounge, 8:00pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1974-11-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Ali Mazrui, World Culture and the Black Experience. Tressider Memorial Union, 8:00pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1974-02-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Ronald Bracewell, The Galactic Club: Intelligent Life in Outer Space. Tuesday Evening Lecture series, 1974-04-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Dr. Carl Djerassi, What Will Human Insect Birth Control Look Like in 1985? Memorial Auditorium, 8:00pm. Tuesday evening Lecture Series, 1974-12-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Robert Bush, Research and Development in Education. Tressider Memorial Union, Room 281-282, 8:00pm. Tuesday evening Lecture Series, 1975-03-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - George Schultz, Leaders and Followers in an Age of Ambiguity. Tressider Memorial Union, 8:00pm. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1975-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. [David M.?] Kennedy Speech. Dinkelspiel Auditorium. Tuesday Evening Lecture Series, 1975-11-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - United Nations Conference
    - UN Conference, Charles Malik Reel 1 #2, 1971-01-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - UN Press Conference. Reel 2, 1971-01-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - UN Conference, Peter Baner. Reel 3, 1971-01-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - UN Conference. Cleveland P.U. Reel 4, 1971-01-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - UN Charter, Hoover Conference, Bishop Auditorium, 10am Reel 5, 1971-01-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
    - UN Conference, Hambro Speech Reel 6, 1971-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Various Speakers. Pre-Moratorium Vol. II, 1969-10-14; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Barbara Ward, Carl Djerassi [year illegible, possibly 1970], 19uu-10-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - James T. Watkins IV, Stanford Begins to Look Back. Stanford Historical Society. Ceras 204, 1978-11-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Raymond Freed West Memorial Lecture series
    - Prof. Jurgem Moltmann. Bishop Auditorium, 8:00pm. West Lectures, 1974-03-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Jurgem Moltmann. Jesus, Son of Man. Bishop Auditorium, 8:00pm. Raymond Freed West Memorial Lecture series, 1974-03-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Prof. Jurgem Moltmann. Bishop Auditorium. West Lectures, 1974-03-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - John Pierce. West Lectures. Bishop Auditorium, 1979-02-20; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - John Pierce. West Lectures. Bishop Auditorium, 1979-02-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
  - Women's Voices at Stanford: An Evening of Poetry. Care of Mike Stillman, Stanford Program for Recordings in Sound. Branner Dining Hall, 8:00pm, 1976-04-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)